Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No animals were harmed
during the production.
Episode 99
Great tent!
People of Holy Rome.
Gladiator games with Holy
Emperor Andronikos begins.
Those who are born to kill...
royals of the warriors...
the axe of the death...
Nico, whose shield is strong.
Those who are born as slaves...
fight for your freedom!
Hey, you.
Why don't you shout?
If you were silent...
you would be a philosopher.
What was that, Cerkutay?
What did you say?
I said silent horses kick hard.
Not like that...
but close.
Anyway, it worked.
That's what matters.
It will start soon.
We should be ready.
You will shout my
name at the end of the day.
The shows are back!
Why? Rome has to be ready for war.
Rome's power...
will be back!
Let the war begin!
You're planning a game...
and kill for pleasure.
The traitor is here.
- Kill! Kill!
- Kill!
Kill!
One day ago...
"The state...whose heir is Osman Ghazi."
"He will be known to everyone."
"The world will thrive thanks to...
the state that Allah gave him."
The spark in Osman's heart will
be bright for centuries."
"The world will thrive thanks to...
the state that Allah gave him."
"Allah's appreciation will
border his state."
"The world will thrive thanks to
the state that Allah gave him."
"The state whose hands are silk
for the oppressed...
and whose punch is hard for the cruel."
"The state whose hands are silk
for the oppressed...
and whose punch is hard for the cruel."
"The world will thrive thanks to
the state that Allah gave him."
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam.
Thanks to Allah...
we saw these days.
We'll set our first council today.
We know grace comes from Allah.
Our one and only wish is to work for it.
My Sheikh, come here, please.
May Allah make your way to spread
Allah's orders easy for you.
Amin.
May Allah let the valiants who
serve Islam succeed.
Amin.
Amin, my Sheikh.
May Allah make this animal holy...
like the ovis (ram) that is
sacrificed instead of Ishmael.
Amin.
Allāhu akbar.
(Allah is the greatest)
La ilaha illallah.
(There is no deity but Allah.)
Allahu akbar wa lillahil hamd. (There is no
deity besides Allah and Allah is the greatest.)
Allahu akbar.
La ilaha illallah.
Allahu akbar wa lillahil hamd. (There is no
deity besides Allah and Allah is the greatest.)
May Allah accept it.
O, people! Bayındır Bey is coming.
Respect the Bey.
Welcome, Bayındır Bey. We're
pleased to see you.
Welcome, my Bey.
Welcome.
Salam Alaikum.
Yenişehir, huh?
Yes.
Osman was in the tent. Now, Osman
rules the city.
Mashallah.
Say Mashallah, Bayındır Bey.
People would think you're jealous.
Mashallah.
I'm happy he's growing.
As he grows, we grow too.
Who will we support if we don't
support Osman Bey?
Whatever you give to Osman Bey, you'll
take back the double.
We always supported him.
Inshallah...
we get what we deserve.
You will.
As long as we support Osman Bey...
it's his fault if we don't
gain anything.
You're right.
Come on.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (in the name of
Allah, the merciful and compassionate.)
Even İnegöl is ours now.
We have the fruits of our labor, huh?
Yes but...
I'm afraid if we pluck them too early.
What fruits, Beys?
The fruits are plucked.
Trees are billets, billets are ships now.
We are against the heathens in waves.
As Osman Bey is here...
don't worry.
May the peace of Allah be upon you.
O, the owner of everything.
My Allah.
Everything you grant us comes from you.
It's yours.
My Allah...
I want to rule these lands
that you gave me...
properly.
Don't disappoint me.
My Allah...
let me rule these lands ethically.
Grant us the dare to look at our Prophet
on the day of judgment (doomsday).
Amin.
Osman Bey!
- Salam Alaikum.
- Alaikum Salam.
Sit down.
From now on, the meetings for
urgent problems are history.
The era is new. The regulations are new.
In the names of Allah's 99 names...
who hold us responsible for our
victories...
I'm opening the council.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (in the name of
Allah, the merciful and compassionate.)
Tell me what's happening.
The migrants are coming.
As they keep coming like this, we won't
have enough weapons during the war.
Mashallah.
They will come with their plentifulness.
Blacksmiths are at their place.
Bayındır Bey...
tell me what is happening.
We have lots of swords, thank Allah.
What about Karaağaç place?
Tell me.
It's good, my Bey.
People eat what they sow.
Karaağaç is important.
It's neighbors with the heathens' place.
It's in barren lands, unlike Marmaracık.
Why Marmaracık matters, my Bey?
It's the door.
A leg of Constantinople limps.
We'll start to conquer before them.
Constantinople
Emperor Palace
Osman doesn't stop.
Won't stop.
He may be getting
ready for a war now.
We have to move before him.
We can't. I'll deal with Osman
for now, Kantakuzenos.
You can't rule Rome with fear.
The Papacy is ready to help us.
We can build a Crusader army and fight
our enemies if we want
Only fools forget what happened.
Do you expect me to trust those Catholics?
They are like our enemies.
Be brave, Emperor. Will
you deal with Turks?
They will come if we don't go.
Enough!
How dare you question Emperor's courage?
How dare you, Kantakuzenos!
If I fight with the ones in hell, I won't
carry it to heaven.
I want to destroy them.
I always support you.
If you excuse me.
I support you.... because...
If they see that we lose our ability, they
will attack us.
That's why we will put up
walls out of stones.
The duties you'll have...
will be those walls' stones.
Orhan Bey...
it's time to experience your knowledge.
Karacahisar Castle is under your rule now.
Let us see what you do.
Your command, my Bey.
Alaaddin Bey.
Continue your education.
Your command, my Bey.
You're the commander
of Yenişehir, Aktemur.
Your word is my word, my Bey.
You have so many responsibilities.
Beys.
We'll build a new bazaar in Yenişehir.
Merchants will come.
Even people will come offshore.
That's why
we will have so many responsibilities.
Turks need trade, my Bey.
You can have our goods.
The golds we earned from the war.
This is a council, not a public purse.
Give those to the poor people.
There's no one in need in our lands.
Everyone is good thanks to you.
I gave those to people in need.
This is what is left.
Then, give those to Karaağaç people.
He said they are in need.
Thanks, my Bey.
A Bey's word is a
command, tell us what to do!
Mongols in the east, Rome in the west.
They are attacking us from both sides.
If we don't stand still upright...
then we will be trapped under the debris.
We're not afraid.
This is such a big plane tree
that it grows every day.
Oppressed people will
rest under its shadow.
Of course, people will try to harm it.
If we don't unite under its shadow
and don't attack the enemy...
then, cruel people's shadow will be
over us.
Beys are working.
The fights for the throne still continue.
We are with the oppressed people.
We know we're alone but loneliness will
hold us together.
It will give us strength.
We live for this dream and move.
We bring justice, we can't stop.
Beys...
if we stop, then we'll stay behind.
We'll attack the heathens
as long as we breathe.
We'll kill cruel people as
long as we breathe.
Until we keep the Islam
flag flying.
Yes, Bey.
Flags will fly as you say so, Osman Bey!
- Can I come in, my Bey?
- Come in.
My Bey, they will move the next day.
We are waiting for your command.
The council is over.
Everyone go back to your work.
May it be easy.
What did Osman bey read?
He ended the council.
We can't know.
We can't figure out either.
Yes...
it must be important.
It's from Konur.
It's about Constantinople.
People who want to
dethrone the Emperor took action.
Emperor being on the throne
helps our conquests.
Get ready.
We're going to Constantinople.
My valiants. What are your duties?
My brother is responsible for Karacahisar.
Mashallah.
Mashallah, my son.
Mashallah, my brother!
So, my Alaaddin?
What is your duty?
I don't have any.
I don't have any duty.
Don't say that, brother.
Our father wants you to be good
for the state that he'll establish.
You're right, my brother.
Osman Bey said so.
Get ready, Alps.
We're going to enemy lands.
We know them well, my Bey.
We'll get through it.
Yes, Kutan.
Come on, it's time.
You're ready, Alps.
Mashallah.
Your food is here.
Cerkutay.
The biggest meal is yours.
I'm not hungry.
I won't eat it.
You will. You should.
I said I'm not hungry.
I won't eat. Don't you hear me?
I'm full.
Okay. I made fried meat.
So much.
There is calf's tongue in it.
I'll take it back.
I'm going back, Cerkutay.
Won't you take it?
I can't go there hungry.
Yes! Eat it so you can fight the enemy.
Cerkutay.
Come on.
My name is Cerkutay.
Cer-ku-tay.
Yes.
Yes. I said so.
Cer-gu-day.
Eat.
You should eat.
You should.
I can stay hungry but you should eat.
I sent you on so many expeditions.
It feels like the first time every time.
Our enemies increase every day.
Our expeditions increase.
We grow, thank Allah.
So is our children.
They even attended their first council.
Mashallah.
They grow up.
My Bey.
I want to...
say something.
Tell me, my Bala.
Tell me.
May Allah speed you.
I was going to say "May Allah speed you."
May Allah help you.
May you succeed.
Thank you.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Alps!
Come on!
My Alaaddin didn't seem good.
How's he?
He was offended.
However, he'll be fine.
Inshallah.
Don't worry, my Bala.
Osman Bey knows what he's doing.
Alaaddin will understand it.
What will we do now?
I might go to the bazaar.
Today, the goods will be there.
Okay, then.
We'll go and check the
goods for the bazaar.
We should check them.
Good.
Come on.
May it be easy.
Come on, Hatuns.
Constantinople
I don't want any trouble.
Tomorrow, the sun will rise in Rome again.
This is the boat we'll use, my Bey.
We will arrive in
Constantinople before noon.
We should be careful.
May our war be holy.
Amin.
Öktem Tent
Thank you, Hatuns.
The cheese is delicious.
Let's check the saddles
before Bengi Hatun comes, Aktemur.
It doesn't look fine.
Let's look at it on the horse.
It's thin.
It should be thick so it will absorb
horse's sweat.
Where is Bengi Hatun?
Didn't you tell her we came?
We did but...
Welcome, Malhun Hatun.
Sorry.
We'd welcome you better if we knew
earlier that you were coming.
Come, drink our Ayran.
Thank you.
We're not here to sit.
We're here to check the
goods for the bazaar.
However, we don't like what we see.
What is this saddle?
Why don't you like it, Malhun Hatun?
It's the same.
It can't stand in balance on the horse.
How can I send this to the bazaar
when I can't even...
let my Alps ride this?
Malhun Hatun!
Alçiçek.
Give me your best Alp.
So that I can show him how to ride a horse
with the saddle you don't like.
No need, girl.
Can I, Malhun Hatun?
Follow me.
There's a big tree outside the tent.
We will race from there.
Come on!
Show me your talent.
Tell me your name before I win.
I want to know who I will defeat.
Aktemur, son of Gündüz Bey.
Thank you, Temur Bey.
Come on!
Mashallah. my daughter.
She's good.
See, Malhun Hatun?
I defeated your Alp
on the saddle you don't like.
I see, Alçiçek.
I see.
Mashallah. You're good at it.
However, you're callow.
You don't even see the wound of the horse.
This is why Aktemur fell behind.
A horse is Alp's wing during the war.
What happens when that wing breaks?
Constantinople
Constantinople!
Brother, would you want to hear azan here?
Inshallah, brother.
This is the best wish.
This is what war is for.
If we try and unite, we will
hear azan here.
Look at the moon.
It's above the cross.
If Muslims unite after this flag...
the azan will be heard not just in
Hagia Sophia, in everywhere.
Welcome, my Bey.
Thank you.
It's ready.
This way.
Welcome to Constantinople, Osman.
Öktem Tent
Oh, Hatun...
why is this anger for?
Do you want to cripple my leg again?
My mother is angry at Malhun Hatun.
As Malhun Hatun is in a
palace, not in a tent...
she's showing off.
She reprehended me in front
of my people and in my tent.
How dare she?
Why?
She said our goods are bad.
What is bad?
If she wants to find it bad, she can.
She said saddles hurt the animals.
My Bey.
Batur Alp and Bayındır Alp is here.
Let them in.
Hatun.
Look at me.
Osman Bey really cares about the
bazaar and the goods in it.
He checks everything.
Send the best goods to the bazaar.
This way, my Bey.
So, Osman Bey wants you to send
Alps to Karaağaç.
It's close to Makli, I get it...
I do but...
I don't know why he sends Alps to there.
You only hear what you want to hear.
Didn't he say in the council that...
Karaağaç is the heathens' neighbor and
Marmaracık is important?
He did.
Then you gave a duty to Batur.
You should have gone there.
I would.
What I bought must have
discouraged you, Bayındır.
I don't become satisfied.
Send your Alps, Ökten Bey...
so that the conquest will happen
and we will have money.
Your love for loot is more
than your love for war.
- Batur.
- Yes, my Bey.
The duty is yours.
Karaağaç is ours.
Makli belongs to heathens.
However, protect it like
it's your own land.
If Osman Bey told to send Alps there...
he must have felt something.
Be careful.
Your command, my Bey.
I take the road in the morning.
My valiant brother.
He will do his duty appropriately.
Tell us, Konur.
The palace is there.
The arena is there.
Commander Sen Tahor should be the one.
However, we don't know what it is.
We should learn.
They will talk tomorrow.
However, you will check the slaves.
When we protect the Emperor...
you will send those slaves and make
them attack Sen Tahor's soldiers.
Your command, my Bey.
Emperor will sit here.
This seat is for you, my Bey.
It's close to Emperor.
Then...
Boran will be behind me.
Yes, my Bey.
You...
will be right in front of me.
Tell me.
Are they ready to support me?
Vatican will support the person
who will revive Rome.
You tell me. Are you ready?
Always.
Emperor will die in the arena tomorrow.
Rome will revive.
Turks nightmare is about to begin.
How will it happen?
Commander Sen Tahor.
A real soldier who
wants the best for Rome.
He will serve us in the arena.
I greet you with respect, Cardinal.
If you want our support...
we should see you have the throne.
Then, we will give you the power
you want, Kantakuzenos.
I won't stop until I take
the lands from Osman back.
I give you victory.
Son.
Are you fine, my Aladdin?
Mother.
I can't fight as my brother does.
I am not strong like my father.
I seem weak and clumsy.
No one will listen to me, will they?
You're wrong, my valiant.
You're wrong.
Look.
Look at your five fingers.
They are all different, right?
They have all different roles.
Also, you are a decent fighter.
Why are you thinking like this?
No.
I am not, mother.
My brother always defeats me.
He wins every duel between us.
I can't defeat him
no matter how hard I try.
I am weak.
Look at me.
You are neither weak nor clumsy.
Power comes from bravery, which is
standing against the cruels, son.
Strength doesn't come from arms.
It comes from here.
Then why...
...my father didn't give me a mission?
What do I lack
that my brother doesn't, mother?
Do you envy your brother?
I was going to give my brother a gift...
But it turns out he just envies me...
...Instead of appreciating me.
I don't envy him, mother.
That my brother receives roles
makes me happy the most.
I just want to know what I lack.
My father doesn't trust me, mother.
He thinks I am weak.
I know it.
This is why he doesn't give me roles.
Aladdin.
Son, Aladdin!
Constantinople
Not only fighters will bleed today.
They have a game here.
And we have come a long way to
ruin their game.
Let's go.
Hello Ürgen Hatun!
Hello to you!
Leave it there.
Now it's your chance to show your skills,
Kayi Alp.
Tell me your name before
I kick you under the dust.
Gunduz Bey's son Aktemur.
Keep blending.
You have been playing with your meal.
Will you ever eat?
Tell me now, what's wrong my Bey?
Nothing wrong, Ürgen Hatun.
Is it because of yesterday's defeat?
I heard that Alcicek beat you.
Help me understand.
Aktemur Bey, who defeated countless Alps,
is defeated by a tiny girl. Is this right?
It was more like a give up for her.
She was very eager.
I didn't want to upset her.
Or I would...
Or what?
- Or you are in love!
- Ürgen Hatun!
What are you talking about?
There is no such thing as
"love at first sight"
I don't even know
if she loves someone or not.
So you say she is for you
if her heart is empty.
Yes.
May your path be clear, my Orhan.
May my Creator protect you.
You have been a good sister to me.
This is for you.
Protect yourself while I'm gone.
Brother, this is your favourite dagger!
So you're just giving it to me?
Thank you!
You are entrusted to Allah.
You too, son.
Alps!
Awaken!
As you order, my Bey!
Let's go!
Praise be!
We witnessed him become a Bey.
May my Creator let us witness
having a grandchild as well.
Amen, my Ayse.
Amen.
You always take it to the bride somehow,
Ayse.
You are talking about Orhan...
...but you want Aktemur to hear as well.
Right?
I want him to hear but
he just doesn't listen, Bala.
He won't hear me.
Constantinople.
Great Rome!
Kill him! Kill!
People of Holy Rome!
Supreme Emperor Andrikos' Gladiator Games
is about to start!
They were born to kill.
The most noble warriors.
Rufuz the axe of death!
Diko the shield!
Slaves from birth!
Fight for your freedom!
Kill! Kill! Kill!
Hey, you!
Why don't you cheer!?
"If you stayed silent...
...you would be a philosopher.
What was that, Cerkutay?
What did you say?
I said "Silent horses kick hard"
Not exactly this line, but...
...something like that, I guess.
It worked.
That's what matters now.
It'll start soon.
Get ready.
Long live Emperor!
You'll cheer my name at the end of the day.
Removed shows came back!
Why?
Because Rome needs to be ready for a war.
Rome's might will come back just like
this removed show!
The fight shall begin!
You play games.
You shed blood for fun.
The traitor went in.
Kill! Kill! Kill!
Emperor Andranikos will kneel!
And everyone who supports him will die.
I need brave men!
We will bleed for Rome today!
My soldiers!
In Rome, the sun will rise again today!
- For Rome!
Come on commander, where are you?
Here is the real commander of Rome,
Sen Tahor!
Kill! Kill! Kill!
Get out of my way!
What's happening!
Protect the emperor!
Emperor Andranikos!
The throne belongs to the brave!
Soldiers! Attack!
Boran!
- I'm here my Bey!
- Off we go!
You traitor!
How dare you!
Boran!
Osman Bey
You learn how to howl
when you have a wolf friend.
Come with me, Emperor.
Emperor!
I will save you, Emperor.
How are we going to get out, Osman Bey?
Emperor!
Come on.
No.
Come on now!
My Bey!
Are you fine, brother?
You're fine, right?
I am. I have just become a Ghazi.
My Bey!
We are with you until the
reinforcement arrives, Emperor.
Okay.
Come on.
Protect the Emperor!
Sentor!
Kantakuzenos!
You low dog!
You betrayed our plan, Kantakuzenos!
Calm down, Sen Tahor.
I will save you from this situation.
You will let me go.
Or I will crush you!
Don't let that ignoble run away, alps.
Kantakuzenos!
You will not talk and I will
get you out of dungeon.
You're late.
I just caught the traitor.
Let's take him to the emperor.
Let's do it.
Come on.
Hang on, valiants!
Neither we nor your valiants have
no power left to hang on, Osman Bey!
We can hang on
but where are your soldiers?
The attackers must have moved them away.
They should be here soon!
Dog!
Who is behind you!
Tell me!
You can't escape your death
even if you figure that out.
The throne belongs to its real owner.
You will talk.
Take him to the dungeon!
Beat him up so that he speaks.
Osman Bey, I want to host you in my Palace.
It's good that you invited us.
We were not invited while
we were on our way here.
Come on. Let's go.
Good.
Did you really give us the remotest place
of the bazaar, Ayse Hatun?
Not at all, Bengu Hatun.
The stalls are separated
according to the goods.
And this is your place.
I don't want this stall.
Is this what you give us
in return of everything we did?
Give us one of the first stalls
at the enterance.
Hatuns!
What is happening here, Hatuns?
Your voice reaches to the other end
of the bazaar.
Well...
...you gave the remotest, the most corner
place of the bazaar, Malhun Hatun.
Bengu Hatun.
We catagorise the bazaar according to the
type of goods.
We do everything for you.
Competition brings fruitfulness.
Tell me about the saddles, Bengu Hatun.
I hope they're not like the last time I saw them.
We completed the goods, Malhun Hatun.
There is no lackings.
Alcicek. Bengu Hatun's daughter.
Welcome.
Unload them.
Masha Allah! (praise be!)
We trusted your words and came here.
Who is going to visit this
fasty isolated place?
Once in a blue moon.
He set up a great bazaar, but...
...who is going to come here?
Who will buy all these?
He sent a messenger to overseas, he says.
Osman Bey must know something as
he set it up here.
You are the one who says we must trust him.
We must, but...
...we need him to make us rich.
Osman is hungry.
He is like a child in a sweet shop.
So you won't sell in this bazaar?
Oktem Bey, I expect nothing
out of this bazaar, so I won't invest.
Crafty you are!
You would invest everything you have...
...if you were sure this bazaar
would work.
I am not saying anything else.
Hey my brave soul brother.
My mother's memorial.
You visit many villages, but
you haven't found a bride yet.
I will find one for you.
I want to see you married.
Don't think about these, sister.
It's time to go now.
Osman Bey commanded.
We will protect the Makri borders
in the name of Oktem Bey
Give me your blessings.
I do, my valiant brother.
Come here!
Yes, my Bey?
Follow Batur.
We need to know what happens
in Osman's distribution of goods.
Yes my Bey.
Constantinie Emperor's Palace.
Get out!
Soldiers, get out!
How did you know this was going to happen,
Osman Bey?
What we already know doesn't matter.
We are after what we don't know.
Why would you do this for me?
Why do you want me to
stay on the throne?
Isn't an unexperienced emperor
better for you?
Kantakuzeros.
My daughter Ofelia.
Or someone from the dynasty.
We have been in war for a long time.
We lost many valiants.
You know the war very well, Andranikos.
But...
...your presence supports the peace.
How unlucky I am to...
...get attacked by my people...
...and to be saved from my enemy.
No.
You are a lucky man.
You have a friend like me.
I appreciate that.
But why?
They could kill me in my bed
while I was sleeping.
They want you to hand the merchant.
A dead emperor only causes disorder.
Now tell me.
Who wanted your throne?
If you give up on your strength...
...there will be many more who
set their eyes on your throne.
But if you stay strong...
...nobody will dare.
Strength...
...comes from trade.
What do you mean?
Emperor.
The caravan coming from China to
Constantinie...
...will pass Yenisehir.
I will set up a great bazaar there.
They will buy Turkmen's goods.
But I will rule this bazaar.
Turk goods are popular in my city.
I accept.
However, you will sell us cheaper.
And the security of caravans is
your responsibility.
Your job here is already hard.
Don't worry.
I will secure the caravans.
We have made a strong ally, Osman Bey.
But we have to find the enemy.
Sen Tahor!
He is a pawn.
There is someone else behind him.
Who is that?
We'll find out together.
Whoever this is...
...his dog Sen Tahor Revealed.
Now he must find a new ally.
Odin wanted our soul.
We gave it.
Now its our turn to take.
Frig.
You are a gift from tetchy oceans.
The most beautiful among the Goddess'
You happened to me from
the wrathful mountains...
...my brutal tiger.
Trudi!
We are from the same mother!
But I have three siblings now, not one!
Saga!
Where is Saga!
He is coming soon!
Let him come.
I know why he is here.
A gift for you.
Easy!
I am still the commander of this city!
You must respect me!
Do you hear me?!
Respect me!
Who are you?
I asked who you are!
I am your death.
Glances of deads...
...are beautiful.
A gift from my Goddess to you.
We saved your life, Kantakuzenos.
We saved the new emperor of Rome.
Sen Tahor.
Whose dog were you?
Damn it!
Who did it?!
Sen Tahor's information was going to
reveal someone.
I was going to have a target
if we were able to make him talk!
Now I will burn the whole city!
No, Emperor.
Calm down.
We will overcome this together.
How, Osman Bey? How?
I was about to lost my throne
at the show!
And my captive dies in my dungeon!
Who am I going to trust?
You need to speak only to your
trusted people.
We will be with you, Andranikos.
We will not let those jackals
eat you.
I appreciate this, Osman Bey.
Always be careful.
My Alps will be around the castle
just in case.
Now...
We got to go.
May your path be clear.
Eyvallah (thank you)
Sen Tahor.
Everything was private.
How did you find out?
I also know that Turk Osman
ruined your game.
How?
The Gods of north whispered me.
You did everything I wanted.
What do you want?
I don't let a lion die against many hyenas.
And I won't let the cowards
take over the brave.
Why do you do this?
Because only the brave can eat
at Odin's table.
What do you want from me?
More than what you offered to Sen Tahor.
An army.
We will give you the throne.
You will give us your army.
Cheers.
Cheers to what?
To my unsuccess?
To Osman's death.
Brothers!
All the masters who taught us to fight
have died!
They are waiting for us
on the other side.
Always remember who you are
and where you are coming from!
Your armors cannot stop...
...the wrath in your blood!
Let your wrath come out and
kill them!
Odin wants this!
Olaf wants this!
Death! Death! Death!
Teger.
They are coming.
You are approaching your death, Osman.
Brothers, let's go!
Hello!
Enjoy your new stall.
Thank you.
So you are Alcicek Hatun.
Yes.
Who are you?
I am Ülgen.
Osman Bey's mansion's cook.
Hah, I know you.
Praise be!
Those are beautiful.
I wonder how your dowery looks like!
Men won't let such a girl stay unmarried.
There are no man to dare to marry me,
Ülgen sister.
Masha Allah! (praise be)
But you might be wrong.
Tell me what kind of valiant you want.
For example, I want a man who
eats the whole caldron.
I haven't thought of it.
But I am a picky one.
First of all, he must fight
as well as I do.
I want a valiant who would accompany
me in a war, not who would stop me.
There is someone like this!
You already know him!
Inegol Martyr Gunduz Bey's son Aktemur!
Aktemur?
The one I crushed?
Mashallah.
You didn't forget him either.
If you excuse me, I need to
see my mother now.
Okay.
This is done!
Holy Creator, I will make those two marry
somehow.
But I need help to marry as well.
Amen.
So Saga is after Osman.
Sen Tahor is already dead.
How did Osman manage to enter
the arena?
How did he know everything?
Sarkis.
He is Osman's man.
I will keep helping you.
Alps! Ambush!
Stay on alert!
Osman!
Fight me like a real soldier!
Fight so that you die early!
We bothered the dogs.
Of course they bark.
Come to me.
Alps!
Don't show mercy until
we arrive in Yenisehir.
Kill everyone you face!
Attack!
Allah is eternal!
Allah is right!
Your death will upset your friends!
Do you see anyone upset around here?
You will drown in your own blood!
They told this to me before.
They are six feet under now.
My place is not in the grave.
My place is in the table of Odin.
Do you think I am hurt?
You are not going to feel the pain
when I kill you.
They will come for you, Osman.
They will come for you.
Let them come.
This land is a grave for the enemy...
...and it's a homeland to our friends.
I promise them the soil under this land.
Alps.
Prepare yourselves.
We are going to Yenisehir.
Eyvallah.
They are coming!
Saga.
Saga! Saga!
No!
Brother.
Saga, saga!
No.
No!
Saga!
Osman killed Saga.
Osman!
Brother, brother!
The flowing water will carry you away.
You will be welcomed in the fairyland.
Your place is Valhalla now.
Your soul is a gift for Odin.
Your blood is...
...ours now.
Give Odin our best.
My little brother.
I swear on you!
If Odin doesn't help me avenge...
...I will walk with the devil!
Our blood shed!
I will not stop before killing many more!
The enemy is different.
Their weapon is different too.
They are new.
However...
I will erase them.
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com